var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "come to you",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "yatikum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "could bring you",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "yatīkum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَجْرٌ",
        "answer": "and a reward",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "wa-ajrun",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "335",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "436",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "437",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "438",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلُوا",
        "answer": "and eat",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "wakulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "532",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "533",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "534",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "He",
        "pcklId": "1367",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "The One Who",
        "pcklId": "1368",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "The One Who",
        "pcklId": "1369",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And for those who",
        "pcklId": "1370",
        "tlit": "walilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1371",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1372",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those",
        "pcklId": "1373",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one",
        "pcklId": "1374",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one",
        "pcklId": "1375",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1376",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1377",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "1378",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) that which",
        "pcklId": "1379",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٍ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "alīmin",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2788",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2789",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2790",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "699",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "and to Him",
        "pcklId": "700",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "[to]",
        "pcklId": "701",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "and to Him",
        "pcklId": "702",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَّنْ",
        "answer": "Who is",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "amman",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَّنْ",
        "answer": "Who is",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "amman",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَّنْ",
        "answer": "or (he) who",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "amman",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَأَمِنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Do you feel secure",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "a-amintum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "do you feel secure",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "amintum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "we believe",
        "pcklId": "538",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِئْسَ",
        "answer": "and wretched is",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "wabi'sa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَارَكَ",
        "answer": "Blessed is",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "tabāraka",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَصَرَ",
        "answer": "the vision",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "l-baṣara",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَصَرَ",
        "answer": "the vision",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "l-baṣara",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَصَرُ",
        "answer": "the vision",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "l-baṣaru",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَبْصَارَ",
        "answer": "and the vision",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "wal-abṣāra",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "baṣīrun",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَبْلُوَكُمْ",
        "answer": "that He may test you",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "liyabluwakum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "518",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٍ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "519",
        "tlit": "mubīnin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "and We have made them",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnāhā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "made",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "and made",
        "pcklId": "311",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنْدٌ",
        "answer": "(is) an army",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "jundun",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اجْهَرُوا",
        "answer": "proclaim",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ij'harū",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجِيرُ",
        "answer": "(can) protect",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yujīru",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَنَا",
        "answer": "came to us",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "jāanā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) fatigued",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ḥasīrun",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنُ",
        "answer": "(is) best",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "aḥsanu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحْشَرُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be gathered",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "tuḥ'sharūna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَاصِبًا",
        "answer": "a storm of stones",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ḥāṣiban",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحَيَاةَ",
        "answer": "and life",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥayata",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَبِيرُ",
        "answer": "the All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-khabīru",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَزَنَتُهَا",
        "answer": "its keepers",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "khazanatuhā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاسِئًا",
        "answer": "humbled",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "khāsi-an",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْسِفَ",
        "answer": "He will cause to swallow",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yakhsifa",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْشَوْنَ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yakhshawna",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقِ",
        "answer": "(the) creation",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "khalqi",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدَّعُونَ",
        "answer": "call",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "taddaʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "nearest",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَرَأَكُمْ",
        "answer": "multiplied you",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "dhara-akum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَلُولًا",
        "answer": "subservient",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "dhalūlan",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِذَنْبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their sins",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "bidhanbihim",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "235",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "236",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَوْهُ",
        "answer": "they (will) see it",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "ra-awhu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَأَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Have you seen",
        "pcklId": "239",
        "tlit": "ara-aytum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَأَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Have you seen",
        "pcklId": "240",
        "tlit": "ara-aytum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "in their Lord",
        "pcklId": "880",
        "tlit": "birabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "881",
        "tlit": "rabbahum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَارْجِعِ",
        "answer": "So return",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "fa-ir'jiʿi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارْجِعِ",
        "answer": "return",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "ir'jiʿi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُجُومًا",
        "answer": "(as) missiles",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "rujūman",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِمَنَا",
        "answer": "has mercy upon us",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "raḥimanā",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmāni",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنِ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmāni",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْزُقُكُمْ",
        "answer": "to provide you",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "yarzuqukum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقِهِ",
        "answer": "His provision",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "riz'qihi",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقَهُ",
        "answer": "His provision",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "riz'qahu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرْسِلَ",
        "answer": "He will send",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "yur'sila",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "زُلْفَةً",
        "answer": "approaching",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "zul'fatan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَيَّنَّا",
        "answer": "We have beautified",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "zayyannā",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَأَلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(will) ask them",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "sa-alahum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْعَ",
        "answer": "seven",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "sabʿa",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسُحْقًا",
        "answer": "so away with",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fasuḥ'qan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَسِرُّوا",
        "answer": "And conceal",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wa-asirrū",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّعِيرِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Blaze",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-saʿīri",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّعِيرِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Blaze",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-saʿīri",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّعِيرِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Blaze",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-saʿīri",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِعُوا",
        "answer": "they will hear",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "samiʿū",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسْمَعُ",
        "answer": "listened",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "nasmaʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمْعَ",
        "answer": "the hearing",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "l-samʿa",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمَاوَاتٍ",
        "answer": "heavens",
        "pcklId": "334",
        "tlit": "samāwātin",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءَ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "335",
        "tlit": "l-samāa",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "336",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "337",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِيئَتْ",
        "answer": "(will be) distressed",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "sīat",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوِيًّا",
        "answer": "upright",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "sawiyyan",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلشَّيَاطِينِ",
        "answer": "for the devils",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "lilshayāṭīni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "you give thanks",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "tashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيقًا",
        "answer": "an inhaling",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "shahīqan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "510",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "511",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "512",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْبَحَ",
        "answer": "becomes",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "aṣbaḥa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَصَابِيحَ",
        "answer": "with lamps",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "bimaṣābīḥa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) companions",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَصْحَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) companions",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "li-aṣḥābi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّدُورِ",
        "answer": "the breasts",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-ṣudūri",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "truthful",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطٍ",
        "answer": "(the) Path",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭin",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَافَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "spreading (their wings)",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ṣāffātin",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَصِيرُ",
        "answer": "the destination",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-maṣīru",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَالٍ",
        "answer": "error",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "ḍalālin",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَالٍ",
        "answer": "error",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "ḍalālin",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "طِبَاقًا",
        "answer": "one above another",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṭibāqan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّيْرِ",
        "answer": "the birds",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-ṭayri",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعْتَدْنَا",
        "answer": "and We have prepared",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿtadnā",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُتُوٍّ",
        "answer": "pride",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ʿutuwwin",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابَ",
        "answer": "punishment",
        "pcklId": "342",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابُ",
        "answer": "(is the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْتَرَفُوا",
        "answer": "Then they (will) confess",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'tarafū",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعْقِلُ",
        "answer": "reasoned",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "naʿqilu",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَتَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "Then you would know",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "fasataʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَتَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "So you will know",
        "pcklId": "358",
        "tlit": "fasataʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِلْمُ",
        "answer": "the knowledge",
        "pcklId": "657",
        "tlit": "l-ʿil'mu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is the) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "820",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلًا",
        "answer": "(in) deed",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "ʿamalan",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(is) with",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعِينٍ",
        "answer": "flowing",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "maʿīnin",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُرُورٍ",
        "answer": "delusion",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ghurūrin",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَفُورُ",
        "answer": "the Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "l-ghafūru",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَغْفِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "maghfiratun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَوْرًا",
        "answer": "sunken",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ghawran",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "unseen",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "bil-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيْظِ",
        "answer": "rage",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-ghayẓi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَفْئِدَةَ",
        "answer": "and the feelings",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wal-afidata",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُطُورٍ",
        "answer": "flaw",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "fuṭūrin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفَاوُتٍ",
        "answer": "fault",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tafāwutin",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْجٌ",
        "answer": "a group",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fawjun",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفُورُ",
        "answer": "boils up",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tafūru",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَهُمْ",
        "answer": "above them",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "fawqahum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقْبِضْنَ",
        "answer": "and folding",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wayaqbiḍ'na",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "qablihim",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرٌ",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "qadīrun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْقَلِبْ",
        "answer": "Will return",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yanqalib",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "Little",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They will say",
        "pcklId": "1558",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلْنَا",
        "answer": "and we said",
        "pcklId": "1559",
        "tlit": "waqul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they will say",
        "pcklId": "1560",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1561",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1562",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "1563",
        "tlit": "wayaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1564",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقِيلَ",
        "answer": "and it will be said",
        "pcklId": "1565",
        "tlit": "waqīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1566",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1567",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1568",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your speech",
        "pcklId": "1708",
        "tlit": "qawlakum",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمٍ",
        "answer": "Straight",
        "pcklId": "659",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُكِبًّا",
        "answer": "fallen",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "mukibban",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرٍ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "kabīrin",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرٌ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "kabīrun",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَذَّبْنَا",
        "answer": "but we denied",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "fakadhabnā",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرَّتَيْنِ",
        "answer": "twice (again)",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "karratayni",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "504",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "505",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "(is) of every",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّمَا",
        "answer": "Every time",
        "pcklId": "375",
        "tlit": "kullamā",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكَادُ",
        "answer": "It almost",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "takādu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we had",
        "pcklId": "1290",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we (would) have been",
        "pcklId": "1291",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "1292",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "1293",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "1294",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَيْفَ",
        "answer": "and how",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "fakayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَجُّوا",
        "answer": "they persist",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "lajjū",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّطِيفُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Subtle",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-laṭīfu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُلْقُوا",
        "answer": "they are thrown",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "ul'qū",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُلْقِيَ",
        "answer": "is thrown",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "ul'qiya",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُمْسِكُهُنَّ",
        "answer": "holds them",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "yum'sikuhunna",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْسَكَ",
        "answer": "He withheld",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "amsaka",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَامْشُوا",
        "answer": "so walk",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "fa-im'shū",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْشِي",
        "answer": "walks",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yamshī",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْشِي",
        "answer": "walks",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yamshī",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Dominion",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "l-mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَ",
        "answer": "death",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "l-mawta",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمُورُ",
        "answer": "sways",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tamūru",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاؤُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your water",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "māukum",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَاءٍ",
        "answer": "water",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "bimāin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمَيَّزُ",
        "answer": "bursts",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tamayyazu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِيرٌ",
        "answer": "a warner",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "nadhīrun",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِيرٌ",
        "answer": "a warner",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "nadhīrun",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِيرِ",
        "answer": "(was) My warning",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "nadhīri",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِيرٌ",
        "answer": "a warner",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "nadhīrun",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَّلَ",
        "answer": "has sent down",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "nazzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْشَأَكُمْ",
        "answer": "produced you",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ansha-akum",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّشُورُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-nushūru",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْصُرُكُمْ",
        "answer": "to help you",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "yanṣurukum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُفُورٍ",
        "answer": "and aversion",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wanufūrin",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَاكِبِهَا",
        "answer": "(the) paths thereof",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "manākibihā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكِيرِ",
        "answer": "My rejection",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "nakīri",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْدَىٰ",
        "answer": "better guided",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "ahdā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكَنِيَ",
        "answer": "destroys me",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "ahlakaniya",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجْهِهِ",
        "answer": "his face",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "wajhihi",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهُ",
        "answer": "(the) faces",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "wujūhu",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَعْدُ",
        "answer": "promise",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "l-waʿdu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَكَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "we put (our) trust",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "tawakkalnā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَدِهِ",
        "answer": "in Whose Hand",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "biyadihi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "67",
        "ayah": "1"
    }
]; 
export default words;